export const questionAnswer = [
  {
    question: "Is a static modular builder for JavaScript applications.",
    answer: "Webpack",
  },
  {
    question: "One of the three pillars of front-end development",
    answer: "JavaScript",
  },
  {
    question: "What invention lets you look right through a wall?",
    answer: "Window",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The science of the structure and properties of various substances and the transformation of one substance into another.",
    answer: "Chemistry",
  },
  {
    question: "A sport that is played with a round ball and a hoop.",
    answer: "Basketball",
  },
  {
    question: " A large animal that has a trunk and tusks.",
    answer: "Elephant",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The capital of the Netherlands, famous for its canals and bicycles",
    answer: "Amsterdam",
  },
  {
    question: "Australian animal with a long tail and a pouch on its belly",
    answer: "Kangaroo",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Legendary British rock band, authors of the songs “Yesterday” and “Let It Be”",
    answer: "Beatles",
  },
  { question: "First planet from the sun.", answer: "Mercury" },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the device that measures temperature?",
    answer: "Thermometer",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the smallest continent by land area?",
    answer: "Australia",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the instrument that is used to measure atmospheric pressure?",
    answer: "Barometer",
  },
  {
    question: "Еhe unit of measurement that is equal to 1000 meters?",
    answer: "Kilometer",
  },
  {
    question: "The coldest, driest, and windiest сontinent on earth?",
    answer: "Antarctica",
  },
];
